<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ENGLISH Blog on Hoa Hong Homestay</title>
    <link>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ENGLISH Blog on Hoa Hong Homestay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 18:23:33 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A poetic and ancient beauty through Dalat Train Station</title>
      <link>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/blog-photos-on-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 12:22:40 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/blog-photos-on-phone/</guid>
      <description>Viral dreamcatcher keytar typewriter, aesthetic offal umami. Dalat train station 5 Let&amp;rsquo;s discover the oldest train station of the Indochina. My home is near the train station. Wherever I go, I always travel by train to seek a familiar feeling. Different from the coach on the ground, the airplane on the sky, the ship on the sea, the connecting railway across the country has its distinctive point. Today, let me tell you a story of a special place of the mountain city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOP 10 cheap homestay near Da Lat Market</title>
      <link>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 17:04:41 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Chil Apartment Address: Phan Boi Chau Street, Da Lat City, Lam Dong Province. Price: VND 2,900,000/6 guests (Up to 8 guests). Book apartment here homestay near Da Lat Market Chil Apartment Chil Apartment is situated on Phan Boi Chau Street, only 500 meters from Da Lat Market. Therefore, if you book this apartment, you will not only explore Da Lat night market but also enjoy interesting gifts from this flower city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bỏ túi những concept party khi đi du lịch thú vị và nổi bật nhất</title>
      <link>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/something-i-need-to-tell-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 17:04:02 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homenkitchen.com.vn/en/blog/something-i-need-to-tell-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ấm áp và đáng yêu với tiệc pyjama Tiệc ngủ là một trong những ý tưởng tổ chức party rất dễ dàng nhưng mang lại nhiều cảm giác ấm áp. Tiệc ngủ là nơi thay vì bạn diện các bộ trang phục lộng lẫy, thướt tha, thì bạn sẽ khoác lên mình những bộ đồ ngủ. Đây là hình thức khá phù hợp với nhóm bạn bè, những người trẻ tuổi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>